# **CURRICULUM VITAE**

### **JAY PRAKASH**

Address –A1/177 Street No-5
Phase-5 Aya Nagar New Delhi-110047 India
Mobile No-9599388290
Email ID-sondhijay04@gmail.com

## Objective

To use my educational knowledge and experience for a good career oriented growth. To work with dedication and become an efficient employee contributing positively to the Organization by constant learning & utilizing my skills and strengths.

### Education

- [10<sup>th</sup> Passed From JIC Kamal Pur Sangla Koti Pauri Garhwal Uttarakhand]
- [12<sup>th</sup> Passed From JIC Kamal Pur Sangla Koti Pauri Garhwal Uttarakhand]

### Experience

1. From June 2007 to Sep 2008

One Year Working at Printing Press Ahuja Creation Lajpat Nagar Delhi

2. From Oct 2008 to Dec 2012

Field Experience in Uni Air Cargo Pvt. Ltd Mahipal Pur Delhi

3. From Jan 2013 to Feb 2015

Sales Executive in Intuoch Care (Vodafone Channel Partner) Kalkaji New Delhi

4. From March 2015 to Oct 2016

Sales Executive in Soham Enterprises (Vodafone Channel Partner) Sec-28, Faridabad

5. From Oct 2016 To May 2017

Sales Executive in Goyal Enterprises (Vodafone Channel Partner) Azadpur New Delhi

6. From Jun 2017 To Currently Working

Business Development Executive in Antriksh Technosys Pvt. Ltd Kalkaji New Delhi

#### **Personal Dossier**

Father Name : Sri Bachchi Ram Date of Birth : 04 April 1989

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Indian

Religious : Hindu

Language : Hindi & English

#### **Declaration:**

I hereby declare that the above mentioned information is genuine go the best of my knowledge.

Place: New Delhi

Date: JAY PRAKASH